Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world is colorful and grand
Truth and falsehood blind our sight
Use your heart to truly see
The truth is not far away
Hey you good or bad, true or false
Can't escape the gray smoke in your soul
Take along all your bravery
Maybe then you'll save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Perfect 3000A
People inside, listen up! You're surrounded!
Drop your weapons and surrender now!
Brothers, boost the firepower!
Let these cops witness the might of the Gold Tooth Gang!
Damn, these guys have too much firepower!
They're arms smugglers—of course they're strong!
3000C, start the operation!
Dammit!
With moves like that...
Could they be the Combat Mech 3000 series?
It's the 3000 series!
It's a 3000C, a 3000C!
No matter what kind of monster you are,
You'll fall before my rocket launcher!
All of you, get up!
The monster's down!
Boss, look!
It's standing up again!
Damn it!
Quick! Quick, the ammo!
Coming, coming, coming!
Hawxing, you worthless piece of junk!
The boss is in trouble! Brothers, help out!
You idiots, I'm not dead yet!
Don't shoot at me!
Hawxing!
You idiot!
Quick, use that thing!
Hurry!
Boss, don't worry.
I'll definitely save you!
Hahahahaha! Poor cops, prepare to die!
Hahahahaha! The Golden Tooth Gang is invincible!
3000A unit, move out!
3000B, C-type combat robots, attention!
Mission deployment begins now.
500 milliseconds after the operation starts,
3000A itself will fire electronic jamming at the enemy.
3000C immediately charges at full speed from the target's left flank.
The target will fire a shotgun blast at 3000C.
The electronic jamming fired by 3000A itself
will affect the target's shooting accuracy.
Mission deployment complete.
Understood.
I am the most perfect, I will complete this mission flawlessly.
Operation start.
Now!
[Squid City News: The 3000 Series Cracks Major Cases in a Row!]
[Ketchup Daily: Large Machines Will Spread Across the World in a Few Years!]
[The Social Security Department Deploys the 3000 Series Robots Again to Bust International Smugglers.]
Now here is our station's street interview report with the public.
The 3000 series is amazing!
We'll never be afraid of cockroaches again!
Robots... robots are terrifying!
Will they wreck my new sports car?
I like Astro Boy.
These robots will destroy our city!
The 3000 series' design and attack methods are too clichéd.
Can't robots in cartoons be more innovative?
That's all for our report.
Thank you, dear viewers
Well, although this operation didn't catch smuggling boss Heidi
The 3000 Series' brave and bold attitude still deserves praise
Supervisor Chen
Yes, it deserves praise
In the next operation
You and your 3000 Series
Must keep up the good work
Yes sir
Oh, right
One more thing
Don't get too tangled up with the media
This just in
The City Security Department
To protect public safety
Developed the 3000-model humanoid robot—
3000A, deploy!
—Last night, it successfully smashed the rampant arms-trafficking organization, the Golden Tooth Gang
Watch me!
3000A is here to save the world!
—The gang's two leaders vanished in the fierce battle
Watch me! I'll destroy you!
Dad!
Be good, Hawxing.
Uncle Heidi accidentally got hurt.
He needs to rest here for a few days.
Get lost!
Boss, don't be angry.
Kids don't know any better.
According to reports,
this is the seventh time the 3000 series has completed a designated mission.
Squid City's Department of Public Security stated
that in the coming years,
they will develop and deploy more humanoid machines with different functions to society,
bringing more convenience to people's lives.
Dad, look!
The 3000A robot is so cool!
I never thought I'd be taken down by a few robots.
Damn it!
Robots.
From now on,
whoever mentions these damn robots in front of me,
I'll kill him.
Boss, don't be angry.
Kids don't know any better.
Cut the crap!
About you ordering the brothers to shoot me during the chaos last night,
I haven't settled the score with you yet.
Don't think I don't know anything
If you dare to pull any more tricks
Watch out, I'll take your son-
What are you looking at?
Go get me something to eat
Dad's going out
Hawxing, don't make Uncle Heidi angry
You hear me?
What are you dawdling for?
Well, hurry up!
Alright, that's our report
Thanks for watching
MojoSpy Discord: https://discord.gg/BkdRezCkxf
Bright eyes are sparkling
Smiles facing the sun
Bravely speak out what's cherished in your heart
That little touch of emotion
Music brings the morning breeze
Carrying away years of wishes
It will quietly settle in the deep silhouette
Quietly stepping at the crossroads of a thousand homes